After the arrival of mother and grandmother's Teej, today my
brother also brought my Teej.  Early in the morning I started doing
household chores.  Because today my brother will
come to give me Teej.  First I washed and
dried the clothes, then finished all the household work and
now it was time to do some quick skin care.
First I tried this face wash which I use daily.
And now it was the turn of this viral D10
mask which I use twice a week.
This is the Safest D10.  Apply it on the face,
let it dry for 15 minutes and then wash the face.
Best combo to remove face tan.  You will get good results in one wash.
I've tagged the screen if you want it too.
Then I took a bath and got ready, then brother Arab
also arrived.  I came and met everyone and we sat and
talked a lot.  And today
I also got to eat a slice of pizza with them.
Now we had to prepare the food.
We had ordered vegetables from outside.  Then
I made rotis and served the food.  He
ate food and gave Teej items to mother.
Now it was time for them to leave.  So she
said goodbye to everyone and went back.